Wygenerowano przez Piotr Wilk-Juraszek

avr-gcc.exe (AVR_8_bit_GNU_Toolchain_3.4.5_1522) 4.8.1
Copyright (C) 2013 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
This is free software; see the source for copying conditions.  There is NO
warranty; not even for MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

GNU objdump (AVR_8_bit_GNU_Toolchain_3.4.5_1522) 2.24
Copyright 2013 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
This program is free software; you may redistribute it under the terms of
the GNU General Public License version 3 or (at your option) any later version.
This program has absolutely no warranty.
GNU ld (AVR_8_bit_GNU_Toolchain_3.4.5_1522) 2.24
Copyright 2013 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
This program is free software; you may redistribute it under the terms of
the GNU General Public License version 3 or (at your option) a later version.
This program has absolutely no warranty.
